Hi, Larry.
How are you?
Good.
How are you feeling?
It's been a rough week, really.
And the best way to take it is to put it
under your tongue and rub
it in your cheek.
Don't do too much.
You're going to be asleep all afternoon.
No, you should do.
Don't try to communicate.
Just relax.
See what happens.
We know from animal experiments
that the inductions cannot be in.
The system is very important
in regulating motor activity.
That very type of activity that is
impaired in Parkinson's disease.
From animal experiments,
we also know that boosting certain
branches of the endocannabinoid system is
helpful in relieving
symptoms of Parkinson's.
Finally, from anecdotal information,
we know that certain patients who smoke
marijuana experience
relief of their symptoms.
I think you're calmed down so quickly.
Isn't it amazing?
He used just a single drop and his hands
afterwards were rock steady
and the Dyskinesia left.
It works most of the time.
Did you guys get lunch really easy?
Marijuana makes me pretty angry
that I can't get it by Allstate.
The number one frustration that I have is
knowing that there is this untapped
potential comes from what marijuana is
teaching us to generate new medicines
and being stuck because of financial
issues or political issues,
that is extremely frustrating.
We now know that medical marijuana
controls Dyskinesia and yet it's not.
It's not available to us.