Do you drink alcohol?
Yeah.
Hearing the smoke?
They told us when you were coming.
They were like, we just
want to let you know.
He'S going to be baked.
That's what he's going
to be fucking baked.
The funny thing is, is that marijuana
gives me energy, brother.
What the same.
You know what he's basically saying?
Marijuana is a hammer.
Some people use it to fall asleep.
Other people use it
to build a beautiful house.
Exactly.
I could smoke on a marathon.
I could smoke on a two
hour and a half practice.
Wow.
You train while.
You'Re high?
Yeah.
I'm going to say yes.
Not all of my practices,
but a lot of practice.
I'm not against smoking a fat one or
maybe like four and then fucking.
Okay.
I don't know if you're allowed to talk
about this, but what is your
favorite off market fight?
I'm talking like, you're at a tackle Bell
and this guy's, like,
chirping at you and you're like.
That'S a good one.
Stating the slap is a good one.
Have you ever caught in the air wall?
Hit the vehicle in time?
It right?
No, but I'm going to have to see that one.
It's a pretty good one, bro.