Still fight, you know, now life's great.
But back then I'm still very
much financially struggling.
And yeah, all I had,
I fight this court case, this legal, this
lawsuit, and that was costing a fortune.
And it's all I knew at that time.
That's one of the craziest stories ever.
That you won the middleweight
title with one eye.
Yes.
And you won it by lying to the doctors.
Yeah.
I was terrified.
I was terrified every time I felt I mean,
I don't want to say too much.
Didn't you fuck with your debt perception,
though, because that's one of the things
that they say all the time.
Like, I'll go and grab
that bottle, for example.
Now I'm fine because my brain touched it,
so I know where it's at.
I can judge it.
But the first time I miss all the time,
I'm always misreading how
far something is away.
Do you know what I mean?
Right.
Because you have the depth perception
and everything's in 2D, and then sometimes
it can fuck with me a little bit.
Sometimes I start getting
a little blurry and like,
I get a little dizzy because sometimes
it's only sometimes all of a sudden
I can't fucking figure.
What about driving?
Driving is fine.
Everything's on the right side
to turn next to you all the time.
Yeah.
If I'm changing Lane,
I always have to give it one
of those until I'm really far.
And I'm always hitting people in the face.
And it's always an old lady the amount
of times because I'm very animated.
Right.
I talk with my hands.
Like, for example,
I'm at a crosswalk in New York City
and I'm in the middle of telling a story.
Oh, my God, I am so sorry.
I've gone like that into someone's face.
And it's always a little
old lady for some reason.
Always they look at me like I'm
the biggest dickhead on the planet.
I'm so sorry.
I am so sorry.
Oh, that's horrible.
Yeah.
But is there any hope for your eye?
No, nothing they can
do in terms of repair.
Well, if you look at that now.
It has gotten worse.
Yeah.
There's just nothing there.
Wow.
When I got this done,
which changed my life in many ways,
to be honest,
I was just sick of looking like that.
You don't see anything out of it?
No light.
Nothing.
If I cover up my good eye and the lights
go on and off, the shade of blackness
changes just ever so slightly.
I can tell when the lights
gone on and off.
That's it.
And there's no replacement lenses
or anything that they can do.
I heard recently that they're putting
in robotic eyes or something like that.
Yes.
But I haven't looked into it yet because
two fake knees and a fake eye.
Imagine if it's better.
Oh, no, I know.
Could you imagine?
I'm fucking back.
Let's go.
I'm back.
One more for the road.
Two fake knees stepping into the Octagon
that would be wild fake
knees and a fake eye.
I think they have
an electronic eye that they've created
that offers superior vision and I think
it's just in the testing phases now.
But see if you can find that,
Jamie I'm pretty sure that it is superior
to normal eyesight and the way
that it interacts with the brain.
I don't understand.
I don't know how it interacts
with the optic nerves
and the signals that it sends.
Yeah, I'm sure it is better with the
technology that they have one day.
Yeah, absolutely.
That's why I retired, though,
because the doctor said and they always
said if something goes wrong
with your good eye, you'll go blind.
You.