O que você está assistindo agora é Mark Zartler cometendo um crime
Para ajudar sua filha, que não pode ajudar a si mesma
Dezessete anos atrás, Christy Zartler deu a luz a gêmeas
Keeley, sua irmã, veio pra casa primeiro
E três dias depois a Kara veio
E eles começaram a difícil jornada de anos
Para aprender a tratar a paralisia cerebral e o autismo severo da Kara
Isto é um anti-psicótico
There are antipsychotics
and enzymes and sleep AIDS.
But few things helped find off the worst
of her symptoms
that could sometimes go on for hours.
Pretty much on a daily basis.
We have some sort of episode
when it's heating up.
I turn off the fan,
have a level eight of a teaspoon.
When Mark found the one thing that could
stop his daughter, he made
this video to show the world.
It takes six deep breaths
and a father's dedication.
The video is the truth, right?
That's typical of what we see.
A neighbor first suggested years ago
that cannabis could ease Keras symptoms.
Mark then found that by grinding marijuana
buds and heating them to 410 degrees
Fahrenheit, it created an immediate rescue
response to his daughter's
most violent behavior.
And by ten, she's usually back out here,
enjoying life again.
For several years,
we were in fear of using it.
Trying it, giving it to her, having it.
But now there is no fear for the dark
Lords, who risked everything by posting
the video of Mark illegally treating Kara.
That more than 120 people have seen.
And by talking to us.
I got to the point where we looked
at the law and said the law is not going
to change unless somebody gambles.
In his post, Mark asks the Texans call
their state senators demanding
a public hearing on Senate Bill 269.
It would expand the access of patients
with debilitating illnesses
to use medical marijuana.
For Kara, that law could make
moments of calm come legally.
And if showing what works for her
puts Mark in jail, so be it.
Okay.
Just saying,
if we want to make a difference
for ourselves and forgive other kids like
Kara, we just said somebody
has to take a risk.
He's another father who will
do anything for his daughter.