One day, I'm sitting in the house
and my son come up crying.
So, you know, when your son come up
crying, you try to think about
before, like, as a grandma.
Is it my Mama,
Kobe, just died in a helicopter crash.
And I was just watching the night before
when LeBron passed him up,
I was like, Yellow Bush.
It's a hoax.
Stop it.
And Shawnee called me crying.
And I said, Hold on, let me verify.
And I called my guy
from the Sheriff office.
He said, that's true.
I stopped crying.
And I'm like, Damn it,
I didn't even haul at him.
Last time we did the sit down,
everybody was waiting for that's.
The last time I didn't get the number,
I didn't text him and Holland.
And that still haunts me.
All the shit we went through,
we could have shook hands and put
that aside because people think
it was worse than it was.
It's just two brothers going at it.
Two guys with difference of opinion always
tell people after my first Championship,
when I go like this,
it's a million mothers in the arena
who jumps in my arms first.
So we hate each other.
How do you have that moment?
But I got a little brother.
We argue all the time.
My cousin live with me.
We argue for a long time.
But the thing that kept
us going was the respect.
When I get double team,
you know, I'm looking for him.
When he gets double team by the room,
he's looking for me.
So you look at our relationship,
it was perfect, but it was non perfect.
Perfect that he made me
play at a certain level.
I made him play at a certain level.
Able to win three.
Did we get along all
the time on the court?
No.
But we know in sports that's
how it is in the locker room.
The only thing I regret
is I got a holiday.
Don't take time to be like,
hey, man, what's happening?
Like a text or something?
I never did it.
He never did it.
And that's what hurt me the most.
I think about it all the time,
and I have pictures of him in my house.
And when I see him take a summit.